Yeah.
Oh, for sure
After the call, I'll share everything.
Yeah.
Sorry, that's all on us. We didn't we didn't get the invite out, so I'm sure…
It's… it's okay.
He didn't realize it was Europe, but…
Actually, on me
No, I appreciate it, but uh…
Yes.
Trust me, I do a lot.
worse stuff than this.
every… I was gonna say every day, but every…
Thanks.
5 minutes, so don't worry about that.
Don't worry about that. Um…
Every song, every so often, right? Awesome. Well, we would love to, you know,
get… keep the conversations going, and talk about…
what we can do to.
make this portal actually work for you on a regular basis.
Um, even when… even… and then, of course, when we add on the franchisees, so.
Did you want to sort of start off and give us.
Uh, you know, something you wanted to discuss that, uh, could help.
You…
Yeah. Yeah, I'm trying to get my notes up here. So, um, just so you guys know, and I'm not sure what Chris communicated with you, but…
After…
we spoke last time, and you guys showed me the stock.
uh… program that you guys had built.
I called immediately, and I was like,
This is super impressive. What can you actually customize, and are you open to…
you know, building something that, over time, we could move our whole operation, not just the…
franchisor-to-franchisee part, but what the franchisees actually…
fully need to operate, and uh…
I hope I'm not over-speaking for him, but he was… he was good with that, and uh…
I said, hey, if… I'm super excited about that, and it's gonna take
time and money to do that, but I would like to at least
start to get a plan on
How we do that, and…
when I have, you know, capital to put towards it, you know, then we can at least be
making progress over time, because it would… it would simplify so many things for us.
Um, so…
Yeah, I already spoke with Chris about it, and I'm very interested in getting
you know, the stock franchisor to franchisee thing live and going…
Right away, um, but…
I was so impressed with it that my real goal is…
getting to be able to use it for how we actually run our businesses.
Not just how we communicate with our franchises and all the franchisees and all that, so I'm trying to get my… I've got pretty detailed, uh…
notes, but the way that Zoom wants to override everything else, I'm trying to look at, I'm…
It's taken me a minute here to get…
those up. Um, but yeah, if you guys are good with it, I'd like to just kind of start…
at a kind of high-level, conceptual overview of what pieces we would need
built in, and then maybe we can…
you know, I don't know how much will get done today, but maybe we can kind of scope out the…
core features. You guys can tell me if I'm crazy for…
thinking we can do any of them, and um…
Yeah, we can maybe just start…
Yeah.
outlining that, um, if I can ever find…
my notes here…
Yeah, take your time, Nick, and um, yeah, we're all on the same page. I mean, I know.
On our last call, when you saw the demo, that's sort of the impression we got.
And Chris did 100%. And these are projects actually that we do all the time with our clients.
Is, um, create, um, you know, um.
Platforms that actually work for them on a daily basis.
Um, across all of their business.
So, um, happy to scope this out for you, put together sort of all the requirements.
And then, and do homework on it, obviously, ourselves, which we'll do.
Yep.
So, it will take some time anyhow, so, um, we'll put together sort of this document.
that, um, everyone has signed off on, and it'll take a bit, because we're going to have to do some research on our end to understand.
your needs, and, um, just develop a timeline.
costs, etc. So, um…
Feel free to, uh…
you know, share your ideas and and.
What your systems do now and can do, and you, what you imagine they can do better and then we can also assist with.
helping in, um, you know, um, providing sort of.
The way the functionality should work, maybe, that could work better for you as well, in this new platform that we could create for you.
awesome. Um…
I do not know why the… I found what I'm looking for, but…
It is just loading and loading, so I might have to just go off of memory here a little bit.
Okay.
Um…
Hopefully it loads at some point, but…
in general, my core problem from a operations platform
standpoint, is…
Right now, we're working off of two programs, at least two programs.
Um, Housecall Pro…
which you guys are probably familiar with.
from somebody else that you've worked with?
Um, it's good for some of the…
Some things we need, but it's horrible for a couple really important things we need, mainly…
the, like, pipeline…
And sales supporting feature, it's pretty good once you get to, like, estimate, scheduled, job, and all that.
Um, but right now, we're using that.
Because it's strong on some things, but then we also…
work off of HubSpot, which is way better for a pipeline and sales… running an organized sales process.
And the more we put locations on,
the more it's gonna be very important.
to have a really good pipeline and sales supporting
piece of it. HubSpot…
I can't really envision us customizing that to take, like, the project management piece,
in, and then get away from Housecall Pro.
But I can't really…
use Housecall Pro,
Because it's got a terrible pipeline feature, and we're not going to be able to do… run an organized sales process. So…
The core, like, reason that I initially was like, wow, maybe you guys can help me,
is… cause…
We're off of two platforms that I just don't ever see either one of them being a one-stop-fits-all.
Um, so, really, from…
Again, I'm basically just working off memory until I get this note to load.
But the starting point, we would need to have a really good
CRM and pipeline that would need to be able to connect with
Our national website need to be able to connect with
the local ads and marketing that we're gonna run, like, per location.
Um, so it would need to… it would need to be a fully functioning CRM and sales pipeline.
But it would need to connect in with…
how website leads come in, how local marketing
Uh, an advertising…
form fills get then dumped into the…
kind of master CRM, and then…
Best case scenario, we could maybe…
do something with zip codes and go, oh, this…
This one came in, and it goes to the Atlanta location because of the zip code, or this one came in and it goes to the Chicago location, because the zip code.
Um, but that… that in and of itself,
would solve a lot of problems, even right now, we're using…
Zapier to connect…
form fills to HubSpot.
But then those leads only live in HubSpot, and then when we actually get farther down the pipeline process,
We're manually moving them over into Housecall Pro, so…
one consistent CRM,
that we can grab everything we need.
solves actually a lot, just being able to do that.
So that's kind of feature one.
I think…
Hey, Nick, sorry, if I can interject there, just have a couple questions to clarify. So at HubSpot, I'm very familiar with, of course. For the Housecall Pro, is that primarily you're using for sales pipeline, or what is the core function that you currently use Housecall Pro?
Uh, Housecall Pro…
terrible for sales pipeline. That's why we use…
HubSpot for the sales piece.
Housecall Pro has a really good…
price book, estimating feature,
proposal feature, and then once something is awarded,
It allows us to schedule it and assign a crew.
Assign job notes,
And it's… it's pretty good from the…
estimating through project management feature.
Got it, okay.
But it only gets me about half of what I need, and HubSpot gets me
Yeah.
That probably gets me 60% or 70% of what I need. HubSpot gets me the other 30 or 40.
And the other… after seeing how
great your program looked,
If… when we're…
I'm really talking about 3 systems. If we don't bring this all under one roof, because all our locations are going to have
access to your system,
So that we can manage the franchisor-franchisee relationship.
Then there's gonna be the pipeline and CRM, which right now is all HubSpot, and then we're gonna have to have the project management
scheduling, you know, proposal, project management, all that stuff.
So I'm really, like, man, working off two systems is hard.
Got it.
we're gonna have 3 systems, sounds like a nightmare, and if we can…
bring all this together in one, we're…
in awesome shape. But, yes, Housecall Pro is good from estimate, proposal,
scheduling, project management?
Um, did that answer the question?
Absolutely.
Yeah, so if I'm here, if I'm understanding correctly, I think we're talking about three different systems here, which you would like to have it in one. So one is basically the franchise management piece, which we have built
Second is the CRM, basically to manage the relationships on the client side and making sure that all the intake data coming in and that data leading into the funnel, we're kind of organizing and managing that through the CRM piece
And then third is the project management, which is basically the day-to-day operations of the business. And what would you like is basically have one system that does all these three core functions, right?
Absolutely.
Oh, okay. Awesome, awesome. Yeah, that's pretty clarified now. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah, okay.
Okay.
And so, apart from… and you mentioned there's, like, other features as well that you would like to
Sure.
Yeah, and this note thing is, uh, not working right, so I'm gonna have to get you these in an email after, uh, and that'll probably help simplify it, but…
First one would be that pipeline that
is connected to all our lead capture forms.
Hmm.
Um, preferably that allows us to…
you know, capture a lead and dump it into a certain stage in a pipeline, create a…
Create a pipeline with stages that I can also assign…
to not only specific locations,
But then that location could assign it to specific sales reps inside of that location.
Um, so there'd be some layers to the functionality there.
Um, but then having that pipeline…
You know, when something comes in, it would be in a really, uh… it would be in an unqualified lead category.
And then there would be different categories through the pipeline. The next one would be
qualified lead…
site visit or sales call scheduled,
estimating and process, proposal delivered…
Um, you know, proposal delivered, follow-up needed,
project awarded…
project scheduled, like, on and on.
And ideally, the stage that we move it through there would kind of control
all the other supporting things in the rest of how the program speaks together. Right now, we don't have that at all.
But, for instance, like, once it's…
a site visit or sales call scheduled.
I would love to build, like,
notifications into…
whoever the rep is a sign that's like,
here's your site visit checklist.
And then they get kind of a built-in reminder of…
Here's just what you gotta make sure you do there. And then they'd fill it out,
you know, get back to the office and move it to estimating.
And then there would be a couple notifications, like,
Okay, um, you know, once you do this, this, and this,
get confirmation from your operations director, or your head of projects before you
send the proposal, and then once they do that and confirm, then it would go to, like, proposal sent.
Once it gets awarded,
then we would want to move it to…
um, like a notification, so to speak, that would be like,
confirm with your head of projects or your operations director on
scheduling this, and then it would be like…
Make sure you… maybe a notification that's like, make sure you attach
this, this, and this to…
the project, so the crew can…
take this over, and…
Um, so that would be, like, the pipeline feature in and of itself, and all the…
kind of the notifications, the flow of work.
Um, but then, like, we would need to build in…
like, on, kind of,
in each stage, like, the estimating stage, it would need to have a price book,
It's preloaded, and I can show you House Call Pros and how they do that.
Over, you know, at some point, um…
But it would be, like, built-in floor system types,
built-in, um, you know, preset pricing that they can modify or customize.
Ideally, it would… once you… once they select what type of project it's gonna be, it would
pull in a preset estimating sheet that we've given it,
Um, it would upload…
the specific floor system specifications,
it would upload trailer load lists and installation checklists, and things specific to that. So each stage,
would kind of… the pipeline would kind of be the master overview that dictates
where things are,
And… but then once… each stage would have all its own…
built-in features, so in that estimating stage, we would make sure we estimate it right, and then it would…
Ideally, have a preset proposal template,
That also has our terms and conditions attached,
And then that would get sent out, and then once something gets awarded,
You know, it'd be, like, project awarded, need scheduled, and then there would
Ideally, populate another checklist that'll be like, make sure you get the client
expectation checklist. Make sure this gets scheduled to the crew, and the right crew gets assigned.
Um, so we're gonna… we would have to get pretty granular on
all the supporting functions of each stage of the pipeline.
But ideally, the pipeline itself could kind of be the control of the whole thing, and then each time it moves,
It's new notifications, new checklists that it populates,
Um, new resources that are…
really easily categorized and accessible.
So that people aren't just…
winging it and trying to remember what they do each…
step of the way. Um…
So, the estimating function's gonna be important.
The proposal sending feature is going to be important.
Um, a schedule that would be specific to
how a job gets assigned
to a schedule, and then how we assign a crew.
or a crew leader.
uh, specific to…
that job on the schedule. So, for instance, uh…
you know, let's say…
we booked a job for this week at, uh…
I don't know, Pepsi. And it's a 7-day job.
So we would assign it to the schedule from…
you know, July 27th to July…
whatever, and then we… so we would assign the project to a schedule, but then we would want to assign a
crew to that project.
And the crew members would need to get notified and be able to see their schedule going forward.
Um, so the schedule feature's gonna be really important.
And then we…
you know, the project management tools and the supporting documents and resources, I'm assuming those would be pretty easy, because it's…
Just building notifications, and…
auto, you know, writing some rules on…
what gets uploaded based on
things that they select. The…
once a… so that's kind of the…
project management aspect of it, but then once a project
is completed, it would then need to move to…
uh, like, invoicing, and we would need to be able to integrate with QuickBooks,
we would need to be able to make sure that that process is all
happen in the right way. Um, I'm assuming since you guys already built the ability to…
integrate QuickBooks and get, like, royalty fees and stuff like that, um, that you've got the functionality of it, it's just gonna be really understanding the specific
Correct.
needs, and how we're invoiced, and how we're closing projects out.
Um, but yeah, the…
Those are probably the core…
main segments of it, but each one, we'd have to get
really granule and detailed on
Yeah
want a part of each one based on… because it's also going to be different based on, like,
If it's a certain type of floor system, it's gonna have
one set of criteria they need to follow. If it's a different one, a totally different one.
But that should be all…
I think that's probably going to be the easy part. If I had to guess,
The CRM and pipeline itself might be complicated,
The schedule could be a little complicated,
And then…
Maybe the QuickBooks part, but…
Yeah.
You guys already…
Yep.
successfully navigated that in a similar…
features, so it's probably…
Probably just more so really understanding what, uh…
what we need it to do. Um, I just said a lot of stuff. Do you have any…
Questions?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, I definitely do. Yeah, I definitely agree that we will need to go granular in terms of each of these kind of requirements. And also, I'm not sure if it is possible for you, I'm not sure right now, or maybe later, where you can give us a demo
Absolutely.
As to how you currently run your operations, like on the several… like, if it's on Housecalled Pro, or I think when you were mentioning about scheduling or estimating, I think we would like to, if it would be possible, we would like to see how everything's kind of currently run, because what I'm hearing is
Yep.
You'd really like to automate all of these things, you know, that you do on a daily basis. And yes, 100%, we can definitely help with that, and we just kind of do need to understand how do you basically do it right now, and then we can kind of scope it out exactly what
the flow would be in the detail requirements would be from that perspective.
Yeah, we can schedule a…
time for me to walk you through
Yep.
both sides of what we're doing, the HubSpot part, the Housecall part, um…
Yep, yep.
Yeah, that would be great. Uh…
That would be extremely helpful, yes, yeah.
Do you think…
that we could build in, like, a AI…
supporting feature in this?
We can, yes, but we will require the main pillar for building that would be the data, right? So, I think my question to you would be, do you have a lot of that data with you that we can
make use of, of course, building the actual functionality for AI is not going to be that tough. It's mainly training the data and training the model, which is basically coming from you, because you are the subject matter expert here, right? Yeah
Yep, 100% we can provide
tons and tons of data on that.
Oh, perfect, yeah, then we can definitely build it, 100%. Yep, yep, absolutely.
When you do that, do you just kind of pick whatever AI
program you're using, and then we would just
by a subscription that…
Allows it to tie into the platform, and then it just…
it looks like it's, you know, all in-house, but it's just…
kind of a pass-through to, say, Claude or something like that, that's trained on our stuff?
So there are a couple ways of doing it. So that is one way and Claude and ChatGPT or the different AI softwares or applications out there, they have built. So Claude is basically a software that runs certain AI models, which Anthropic has built
Okay.
Right? So what the approach here would be, we can do that as well, that we can connect through API, through Claude, or the other way is that we use local AI models and then retrain it with your data.
So it's only specific to your data, your business, and the support that it's providing. It's to your business. And it's not like hallucinating. And we set up guardrails that it's not giving incorrect information and stuff like that because how Claude models and those are trained
Okay.
Those are basically kind of, you know, scraping the entire internet and, you know, searching all the data. So there are multiple ways of doing it, of course. But yeah, we can kind of go more detail into it on exactly what way would you prefer in terms of
Because, of course, getting this AI model, yes, there would be a subscription because it runs on credits and tokens on how many it's used per prompt when user asks a question, for example. So yeah, 100%. But there are multiple ways of doing it, and we can definitely explore different options here.
Okay. One of the things that…
we do in our pretty regular
uh… business…
is, like, take an architectural drawings,
And doing takeoffs with those.
Um, and there's specific programs for that, but lately I'm finding that, like,
Claude or Gemini is actually…
just as good and way simpler.
doing that, so Ideally, like, in part of the estimating
section of it, we would have an AI-assisted
piece of it that would help do what's called a takeoff, which is just…
You know, uh, general contractor might give me 100 pages of architectural plans.
But there's, like, two pages that are actually relevant to me.
And then I ran them through a program, and it says, oh, this project is 5,000 square foot of…
floor, and 500 square, uh, linear foot of cove,
And here's the floor finish.
And if we could, like, build a piece of that in…
assisted by AI,
and have it create, like, snapshots of what's important, and, like, make an installation.
map that then would pass to the next stage for the crews, like that.
that sort of stuff.
I think, based on what…
what feedback you're given. I think probably functionality-wise,
If we can use AI,
that it's… I think it's doable, but it would save us…
so much wasted time, because I'm…
I know I said we got, like, 2 or 3 core things, but if you mention all the, like,
Supporting tools we use,
Yep.
that live in different spots, it's 6 or 7, probably.
Okay.
So if we can, like, replace those with AI…
Inside the platform, it would simplify a ton, um…
Okay.
Another question on, like, can we…
integrate with…
things like Apollo and stuff like that, so that we're not…
Having to give…
subscriptions to, like, 100 locations, we could just have a…
Maybe a spot in there where…
They request a…
prospecting list for their market.
it just ties into our master…
Yep.
you know, Apollo account, and it populates something, and then…
Yeah,
It kind of all lives in one spot, even though… even though you're not building a data scraping tool, at least we can have integrations where
They request something, we approve it. Once it gets approved, it just…
does it, gets it to them, and they're not…
going 7, 8, 10 different places for all these little supporting things that we need.
Got it. Yep, yep, no, definitely we can, we can definitely look into that. And to… to going back to the other, for the AI feature that you mentioned for the support tool, I'm assuming that how you explain, like, the architectural diagrams that you get from a client
All that work that you explained that you would use the AI for, I'm assuming that's all done manually right now, and you basically want to save all that time using AI to help you do that, correct?
direct with the addition that I also don't want to train
100 locations on stuff that I can simplify for AI, so instead of having
Correct.
When we're putting franchise locations on, instead of having to also train
all of the salespeople at all those on how to do takeoffs, and how to…
we can just say, when you need to do a takeoff,
go to this spot in this platform,
give it this document.
And now, not only is it all simplified,
And then they don't need the extra tool, but I also actually…
didn't really have to teach them anything, I just had to
Yeah
Say, tell the… go to this spot,
give it this document, tell it you need this, and now we're good to go.
So, what you said, plus…
a little more simplification.
Got it, got it. Okay, okay. I think that makes sense.
And I do have a couple more questions, but was there anything else that, in terms of features that you would like to
I mean, I definitely wanna…
get… go through my notes and make sure they're simplified, and then send you guys
Sure.
what I think is my, kind of,
A to Z functionality needs.
Yep.
Perfect.
But as far as this call goes,
I think I hit kind of the super generalized buckets that we would need to focus on.
Okay.
I probably missed something, but I'll… I can follow up with that. Like, you guys definitely get my…
core hope here.
Yep. Yep
So, now, once I get you a much more detailed
Yeah.
functionality, hopes and dreams, uh, I think it all made sense, so I'll follow up with
with that, when I…
get to what I'm looking for, but, um…
Yeah, for sure. Yeah
Yeah, your questions were…
Yeah, I have two kind of, they're more, I guess, general questions. So first is
Basically, how I was mentioning before that we're really talking about the overarching three different systems, right? One is for franchise management, one is a CRM, and the other is the project management tool or software, right? But what you would like is, like, one-stop shop so you can do these three core functions in one
Yep.
There are multiple ways of doing it in my personal, and I'd like to hear your feedback on it. My personal recommendation would be not to combine all these features in one platform, because they, like, if we go to a CRM, it has its own set of features
Right? And then combining that with all project management features and franchise management features can get really overwhelming from a user standpoint, a user experience standpoint. It could definitely build in a one-stop shop, 100%, but it would still live in, like, a separate platform
But you would have access through from one shop to, if you want to project management, you can go there, which is for your operations. If you want to look through CRM, you can go through the CRM and look through there, right? I mean, I'm just, this is just my UX brain thinking right now. I totally get what you mean, but this is kind of more recommendation we can more drill down into it when we actually kind of discuss more
granularity and requirements when you do on the following calls. So yeah, I think, I think that's kind of cleared enough. The other question I wanted to ask was, in terms of… and this is more for future, when you talk about customer engagement and building relationships with them, do you also foresee having a separate
mobile app for the clients or the customers? Like, is there something you have, you know, some feedback on that?
in terms of your needs
Um, so, in terms of, like,
When you say customers or clients,
If we're talking about people that are buying floors,
from one of our locations. I don't think we would ever need an app
for that…
In terms of an app for…
or owner-operators.
I think that would be super helpful. Um…
Okay.
Yep.
Like, for instance, obviously HubSpot has an app, and Housecall Pro has an app.
And it's a little bit…
more limiting than the desktop.
capability, but it is super helpful, like, I can click on Housecall Pro right now,
I can go to…
you know, our schedule, I can see what the guys are doing.
Um, so in terms of…
When you say clients, if we're talking about people that are purchasing floors, no?
If we're talking about the franchisor to franchisee relationship, and that…
mobile app for…
Um, people that are trying to operate their floor coatings business.
Got it
That would be awesome, not just for the sales team or the business team at each location.
But it's super helpful for the installers, or the field technicians,
Because, um, you know, if they're on a job site,
Got it.
They need to see the project management-related stuff, and the scope of work that they're doing, and the…
map of where they're installing versus where they're not, and they need to be able to…
upload pictures, which is something I forgot to say. Right now, we use…
a third-party
photo app called CompanyCam.
Where if they…
are logged in to…
the Housecall Pro tool in CompanyCam,
Those speak to each other, so they go into…
the photo app, they take pictures, and then it automatically stores it against
The actual project or job site that they're on.
So the…
not to get off track on what you actually asked,
But, like, the ability for…
installers in the field, or field technicians,
to have a mobile app is…
Really important, and also the ability for the sales team
when they're on a sales call and they can work through a check sheet… checklist of making sure they did all the right things and got all the right info, and got all the right pictures, and…
did all the right testing at that sales call. Um, that's gonna be so much easier.
from a mobile app, um, or…
an app that they can use on a…
Yep
iPad or something like that. Um, so I definitely think a mobile app would be…
where we'd want to go eventually.
Okay.
Um, and then back to…
the… trying to keep them separate.
I think the franchisor-to-franchisee…
relationship management.
Yeah.
Correct.
Those are… that's way different than trying to actually operate the business, so that… that part, I think, could be…
Yep.
separate, but…
one of the… one of the biggest problems I'm trying to solve right now is, right now, we've got
a standalone CRM and a standalone project management,
Yeah.
And… there's so much manual…
moving stuff between the two, there's so much redundancy.
And what should be, like,
a seamless progression. So, like, the CRM pipeline,
isn't only…
a CRM, and then outside of it is…
in the way I would love it to be done, like, that pipeline feature?
Yeah.
actually is kind of the control of the whole project management process.
Because once… once a contact…
And then a project opportunity off of that contact is created,
really, ideally, that would all…
those… that CRM in what we're calling project management,
they… they overlap so much in the estimating sales,
proposal piece of it, so if they're in two different…
places, it doesn't really solve for…
Correct.
what I'm hoping to solve for. Um…
So ideally, that would all be in one…
thing that you guys can help us build, and if…
If you said, hey, as we're scoping all this out,
this needs to be, you know, from…
from sales all the way to project management, you know, let's call it a…
operations platform. Like, if we could get the operations platform all in one spot, but we have to keep the franchise or to franchisee
thing separate. That's fine, that's not a big deal.
Um, but…
Got it.
the… yeah, the sales to project management and everything that connects it in between would be pretty important to keep in one spot.
Yep.
the only, I guess, caveat to say in the franchisor-to-franchisee relationship should be separate.
is, like, things…
One of the reasons I think it'd be awesome to figure out how to have it in one spot is because, like, when they sell a certain type of job,
Now they need a certain type of flooring material.
And if they could order that, and we, as the franchisor, we…
sell that, and we provide that, so if they need a…
you know, they sell a job, and then they need to order material from it.
Well, that's kind of over now into the franchisor-to-franchisee management.
type of thing, and I think, if I remember right,
You guys had a really nice, uh, feature for ordering stuff from the franchisor.
Correct, correct.
Um, and a lot of… in our…
Um, you know, and the way our business is gonna work, a lot of that stuff is gonna be project by project,
as-needed basis. So, if it's like, okay, we, you know, we moved it through the pipeline,
We sold this job, we scheduled it, now we need to order this type of flooring material.
it would be awesome if we could do that.
right inside the project, or right inside the operations platform, as we're calling it.
I think for simplicity, as we go forward, you know, we can say that the FMS platform
Yep.
Which is franchise order to franchisee management, but then this customized thing that we're hoping to build out.
I mean, we could… unless you guys have a better name, maybe we could just loosely call it, like…
our operations platform or something like that.
Yeah.
But, obviously, know that it…
ties in sales pipeline,
CRM features, plus…
estimating, scheduling…
project management, all that. So, um…
Got it.
Yeah, if we could call that, like, the operations platform,
would it be way better if…
we had to go to a different spot and still order material? Yeah, still be way better, and I'd still be ecstatic if we could figure out how to build this.
Yep.
But best case scenario would be we could go, oh, cool, something was sold, they scheduled it, we need to order material,
And they're gonna order it from the franchisor,
And we can do all that in one.
Got it.
But sometimes…
Yeah, awesome. No, I think… yeah, sorry.
Sometimes you just gotta be okay with a lot better, and…
You don't always get best, but uh… if we can work towards
Best case scenario overtime, that'd be awesome, but…
I think, at least based on what I…
saw you guys already built.
And what it sounds like you think you could customize
I know we would be in way, way better shape, and…
for, you know, for a while, I'll…
I'd be thrilled with that. So, um…
Yeah.
Yeah, awesome. No, I think… I think… I think what that's all of this is amazing. And I think we can definitely help you because especially how I've been in the industry for like over 10 years now, so especially all these software development projects that it's always an iterative approach.
Right? So you definitely have that, let's say, end goal vision for your business, for your platform that you would need. And we can… we can start with, like, you know, like, like, first phase or first release is just building, like, small phases, like, break it down basically into phases, and then
Yeah.
Yep.
finally achieving that end goal. So, 100%, and that's exactly… that's exactly the iterative approach, you know, that's, like, the best case scenario that works in softwares, right? So, 100%, 100%. And yes, no, I think we… I think I completely understand, and I do have
kind of clear picture of what exactly you're looking for. But I think next step, as you mentioned, if you can send us that notes that you have for, like, the different features, and also… so we'll start going through that, and also if we can schedule a follow-up call, when you mention that you can walk us through everything on your screen
Yep.
How everything is done. So we would take all that information and then start scoping out all the requirements and also the solution as well, that what the solution for you would look like, right? And then we can kind of go forward from there.
Yep, awesome. Um…
No, I really appreciate all of you making time for this. I'll get you those notes. If you don't mind getting me the recording of this, because I don't think my note-taker was in there, um…
Absolutely, yeah.
I'll get that to Stefan, who will be very involved in this project from our side.
Um, and then…
would love to know when you guys are able to jump on.
Um, to do a screen share of these other couple programs and how we're piecing everything together.
Uh, Stefan probably wouldn't…
need to be part of that. I can see if he wants to, but…
Um, that's more so just helping you guys understand what we're currently doing,
And… yeah, I mean, just…
One step at a time, just getting better.
Helping you guys get better understanding of what I'm trying to accomplish, what we're doing right now that kind of works, but…
Is it ideal? Seems like the next, uh, next stage of it, and…
Yeah, I mean, I love that we're…
Focusing on it and making progress, but I know that this is gonna take…
quite a bit of time to…
move through, but uh, you know, if we don't start somewhere, we…
We don't start, um…
So, yeah, appreciate y'all being willing to start planning for this, and…
I'll get you those notes, and then we can work on when our screen share to show you
These other platforms, uh…
Yeah, just… maybe if you don't mind shooting me some…
windows of, uh, availability, preferably in the afternoon, um, either towards the end of this week or sometime next
week in the afternoon. Um, but yeah, those can be the next steps if you guys are good with it.
Okay, awesome. Yeah, no, that sounds good to me.
Okay, very good.
Yeah, thanks a lot, Laura. Appreciate it.
Sounds good, Nick.
Alright, thanks everybody.
Awesome. Thanks so much.
See you guys, I'll get you those notes.
Talk soon. Bye.
Okay, thanks, thanks.
Awesome. Talk soon, bye.